{
    "subject": "Emilio_Fern\u00e1ndez",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "The_Torch__film_",
    "human_readable": "Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez created the film The Torch.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9160134196281433,
            "question": "What film was created by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8769451379776001,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7950868010520935,
            "question": "What did Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6911446452140808,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6520548462867737,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Torch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6276935935020447,
            "question": "Is 'The Torch' a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4758394658565521,
            "question": "Can you name a film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43761906027793884,
            "question": "Who is the director of 'The Torch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4368457496166229,
            "question": "What kind of work did Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez produce?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3008439540863037,
            "question": "Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez is known for what type of work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez created the film The Torch.",
            "html": "yago_9213_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of work did Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez produce?",
            "html": "yago_9213_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is the director of 'The Torch'?",
            "html": "yago_9213_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez?",
            "html": "yago_9213_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9213_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9213_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9213_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9213_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9213_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9213_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9213_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9213_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9213_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9213_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents indicate that \"The Torch\" was directed by Emilio Fernandez, supporting the statement that Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez created the film \"The Torch.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}